

CONTACT

- +91-7428033046
- shwetpathak324@gmail.com

SKILLS

GRAPHIC DESIGN

- Poster, Logo, Flyer, Brochure, Banners, Stickers, Invitation card, Infographic, Advertisement, Social media design
- · Vector tracing, Vector works

VIDEO EDITING

 Creating content for social media platforms like Instagram Reels, TikTok, and YouTube Shorts.

DATA ENTRY

 Manual typing, Research Proposal, Web Research, Word/Excel to PDF

TOOLS



LANGUAGE

HINDI (Native)

ENGLISH

Shweta Pathak

STUDENT OF LADY IRWIN COLLEGE

PERSONAL INFO

I am a dedicated Development Practitioner with a passion for driving positive change through creative communication. With over 3 years of experience as a Graphic Designer and Video Editor, I have honed my skills to blend the art of design with the power of storytelling.

EDUCATION

(2)	M.Sc in Development Communication & Extension	2022-24
	University of Delhi, Lady Irwin College	

0	B.Sc in Home Science (First Division)	2019-22
	University of Delhi, Lady Irwin College	

SCIENCE (XII)

JD Academy

2018-19

EXPERIENCE

Freelancing	2021-Present
FIVERR, UPWORK	

• Graphic designer & Video editor

O	BRSR	2024-Pr	esent
	Praxis NGO		

Fundraiser & Grant Proposal

DigiSwasthya NGO

2024

•	Social Media Content Creator	2023-Present
	AIWEFA (All India Women's Education Fund Association)	

(Social Media Manager (8months)	2023
_	thehodyclinic (Flen Riyas)	

•	Field Visit and IEC Material Creator (3mon)	2023
	GRAVIS - Rajasthan	

()	Public Relations (2month)	2023
	FIFE organization	

Research and Evaluation Specialist (3months) 2022

Surveys and In-depth Interviews, Case studies

Arpana Trust - Gautampuri

PVR NEST (CSR INITIATIVE)

• Sessions, Interviews, FGD, Story of Change, PRA & PLA Methods

(Graphic Design (3months)	2021

Aashman Foundation